So now that you know the memory structure of mifare classic cards.
We are going to program these cards using ACR 1 to 2.
So this is the tool, ACR 1 to 2.
And we are going to program our card using this tool.
Its price range is in between 25 to $30 and it has its own SDK.
So you can easily purchase this ACR 1 to 2 tool from Amazon or AliExpress.
Make sure with this tool the seller also provides its SDK, right?
So seller will provide the SDK with this tool, and this tool can easily read write Mifare cards.
It can also create value blocks which we are going to see and it can also change keys and sector trailer,
which we are going to see all those things in our coming videos.
First, we will see how we can program Mifare classic card using ACR 1 to 2.
And later on, we will also see how we can program this card using Arduino module with some type of
microcontroller which we are going to see in our coming videos.
So in this section we are going to just use ACR 1 to 2.
And if you are not able to purchase this tool, there is another section in which I have shown how to
program Mifare Classic card using Arduino module.
It's a special type of module which comes with microcontroller.
So make sure you check out that section as well.
Right?
So this section is totally dedicated to 1 to 2 and we are going to use this tool and program Mifare
classic card using this tool.